Why am I in the market?
Gil-dong is here!
Find Gil-dong!
Gil-dong?
What?
What happened to my voice?
Is something wrong with my ears?
What?
Why is your face...
Why is your voice...
Why am I...
What on earth is happening?
How much longer should I wait?
Why won't I wake up?
Why isn't this a dream?
Why on earth
am I in the aide's body?
Let's go to where I was.
I must go to where I am.
But where am I?
Tell Her Majesty that
it's an urgent matter
relating to my marriage arrangement.
Yes, my lady.
May I ask you a question?
We meet again.
Again? It seems like
I'm supposed to know her.
Nice to see you again?
You remember me this time.
Did he not recognize her before?
Of course, I do.
I'm a little lost right now.
Where are we?
We're in the palace.
Palace?
Yes, palace.
Palace? I'm in the royal palace?
The palace where the king lives?
Why the palace, of all places?
I'm not familiar with this place.
I don't know how to get out of here.
You said you knew me.
Can you help me?
Sure.
You helped me last time.
Let me know if there's anything I can--
Thank you.
Where's the next gate?
Hyeopsaeng Gate is over there.
My apologies, but could we make haste?
I must hurry.
Sure.
What a pair of impetuous young things.
But how strange.
The man looks just like my son.
It is unfortunate, Your Majesty.
Send for Magistrate Seo.
Thank you for guiding me out.
And my hands...
Pardon my discourtesy. I was in haste.
Seeing that Your Highness
returned so late,
something must've happened
at the constabulary.
It seems so.
I can go alone from here.
Thanks for today.
Hae-rim!
That's my name.
Hae-rim of the Shin Family.
And my brother is
the Superintendent at the Hyeminseo.
You're the Superintendent's sister?
You don't look like him.
You're beautiful.
If you'll excuse me.
Next time,
please remember my name too.
How did you...
Has my message already reached you?
No, sir.
Pardon?
I mean...
I was passing by on other business.
I threw those into the well.
They found them already.
They're Gil-dong's.
The Chief Censor was
killed by Gil-dong today.
Is that so?
About four hours ago,
he came to spy
on the Chief Censor's residence.
And it seems he was injured around here.
Was I bleeding this much?
It seems his injury slowed him down,
so he discarded his mask and robe
and fled with his true face exposed.
I must've been unconscious for a while.
I wonder if I woke up myself
or someone moved me.
Aide Kang, listen carefully.
Gil-dong
has been framed.
He's been framed?
Do you remember
when the ruffians around Unjong Street
were caught with the silk
they had stolen last winter?
They claimed it was
what Gil-dong had stolen.
I remember that.
Someone from the merchant guild
remembered one of the ruffians,
so Gil-dong was able to clear his name.
There was another case.
There was a rumor
that Gil-dong carried off
the Inspector General's daughter-in-law.
It turned out that she had eloped
with the writing tutor.
So someone used Gil-dong's name again?
I never imagined his name
would be used in a murder.
In any case,
just focus on finding evidence.
Don't be fooled
by the blood-written message.
Yes, Your Highness.
But I haven't reported
those cases to you.
You already know a lot of details,
including the blood-written message.
I happened to hear it in passing.
Is that so?
Right.
Was there any report
of someone found collapsed nearby?
No, Your Highness.
By the way...
Have you been drinking?
I guess I have.
I heard that today
was Physician Hong's wedding.
That may explain it.
I must go now.
Where?
Later!
You can't just go without Officer Seo!
Your Highness!
There you are.
A physician was here too.
Who brought me here?
Let's keep this to ourselves.
Don't tell anyone.
If the elders learn the new bride
was found unconscious outside the house,
it would reflect poorly on her.
All right.
Good thing you found her.
What on earth was she doing there?
Was she trying to run away
because her husband died?
What?
Shut your mouth.
Hey.
Wake up.
Why won't she wake up?
Her heart's still beating though.
Is anyone in there?
Is this body empty?
Anybody here?
Are you there?
What?
Am I back now?
I knew it.
It was just a dream.
If you were really back,
you wouldn't be seeing this face.
Who are you?
Whoever is speaking there,
are you the owner of this face?
Eun-jo of the Hong family?
How is this...
Are our souls really switched?
This doesn't make any sense!
Does it hurt a lot?
How did you hurt your head?
I tripped and fell outside
because it was dark.
How did you get here?
I passed out again
as soon as I opened my eyes.
Just before that,
the Chief Censor's slaves came.
He doesn't know I'm Gil-dong.
Goodness.
How can my own face look so unfamiliar?
Same here.
First, we must find a way to switch back.
We should get out of here.
Can you move?
The sun is up.
Go get some sleep.
Father will be out soon.
I delivered the dinner as you ordered.
I told her to get some sleep after dinner.
Please excuse me.
She looked like
she could die at any minute.
Poor Eun-jo could fall seriously ill.
She might as well just die.
If you just disappear,
it might stir up trouble.
Tell the doorkeeper
that you're visiting your mother.
My mother?
Then, where am I now?
Is this your in-law's place?
Blast.
Why did they have to move you here?
As of yesterday, this is where I live.
By the way, why did they put
the mourning dress on me?
Did someone in this family die?
That...
Well, that's...
Someone's coming.
They might see me, so I'll hide.
Great.
Why that wretch, of all people?
What are you doing here this early?
I mean...
what brings you here, sir?
I came to move the body,
but I guess I came too early.
Oh, no.
The second son?
The body?
Why would the body be here?
Young Master?
Isn't the body supposed to be placed
behind the incense table?
Go check in the men's quarters.
Young Master.
Are you joking?
Not at all.
Young Master.
You've come to the wrong place.
Now, go back, Young Master.
You almost disappointed me.
Because you can't die before I ruin you.
Look...
You see,
I don't quite follow you.
How could a husband
say such things to his new bride?
Husband?
Oh, no...
You're supposed
to love and cherish your bride.
And you said what? Ruin her?
If you had a fight
with your wife last night...
Who is this husband?
What are you saying?
It's you, obviously.
This is getting out of hand.
Enough joking around.
What makes you think I'm joking?
Have you lost your mind?
The husband you keep talking about
passed away last night.
Passed away?
So I'm in this mourning dress
because of my husband?
Then, who are you?
Answer me.
The grandchild of the deceased.
Grandchild?
What brings you here at this hour?
To keep my family under control.
Is that why...
Wait.
If he had a grandchild,
he must've been well over 60, 70, even.
This marriage makes no sense.
Have you really lost your mind?
Or did you finally come to your senses?
Well, obviously...
It's the latter.
Young Master.
I guess
I wasn't thinking straight for a moment
because of the shock.
Thanks for helping me understand
what's going on, grandchild.
By the way,
I would appreciate it
if you could erase from your memory
that I just mistook you for my husband.
To have thought so, even for a moment,
is deeply dishonorable to me.
You've come to your senses,
but what's with this attitude?
Young Master.
Some mourners have arrived from the east.
Go ahead.
The chief mourner
shouldn't be away for too long.
Young Master.
You there, wait.
How are you feeling, my lady?
Do you remember
being carried in yesterday?
Vaguely.
Since I'm a woman,
I don't have to receive mourners.
Please make sure no one enters here
during the mourning period.
I will be visiting my mother.
Don't let anyone know.
Yes, my lady.
You can come out now, Hong Eun-jo.
Climb over the wall.
I don't want to stay here
even for a second.
Where are we going?
No one passes through this path.
We can talk here.
About my wedding, what you heard is true.
The old master was my husband,
and he passed away
right after the wedding.
I know this may sound absurd to you,
but this is common
for people of my status.
I'm sorry for saying
I was to marry their second son. I lied.
I just thought it was for the best.
Because it would help you move on faster
and ease my mind.
Why are you staying silent?
Say something.
We need to find a way to fix this.
I just don't know what to say.
I've been thinking about it
the whole way here,
and there's nothing I can say.
Since I'm nobody to you,
I can't even be angry with you.
And I know how difficult
your choice must have been,
so I can't even blame you.
But I don't want to pretend
that I accept or support what you said.
That this is common.
What's driving me crazy right now
is that I'm not in my own body,
so I can't even just go and drag you
out of that family like a tyrant.
So I must get my body back first.
It sounds like
you will actually do what you just said
once you get your body back.
That is exactly what I meant.
I'm also thinking about
how I should destroy this family
that let this wedding happen
so I can ease my anger.
But what makes me most angry is
that I was completely unaware of this
and gave you the silk shoes,
wishing you happiness.
I'm so mad at myself.
So I'm telling you in advance this time.
From now on,
I will be even more relentless.
I will not hesitate even for a moment.
Let us leave it at that.
You could have
avoided it.
You could have told me about it.
I didn't feel the need to avoid it.
And it's nothing so pitiful
that I should need help.
It is unfortunate that
the ill man passed away
on the day of the wedding,
but I was to live
the rest of my life comfortably,
in their annex as the mistress.
That was until our bodies were switched.
All the more reason
to switch our bodies back.
You have a comfortable life to live,
and I have tyranny to exercise.
We each have duties to fulfill.
That will be our agreement for now.
Madam, are you all right?
The old master has passed away?
Then, what happens to Eun-jo?
She's a young widow now.
Can we bring her back?
She's married now.
She's part of their family.
That means she must live with them
for the rest of her life.
Unless she runs away somewhere far away.
Runs away?
I've never read a story like this
in any book.
I've never heard a myth
or folk tale like this either.
I've been thinking about it,
and this isn't the work of a human.
So this was done by something greater?
As a punishment?
Well, it's clearly not a blessing.
I won't be mad at you,
so please be honest with me.
Have you done something bad lately?
No.
And even if I have,
why would you be punished with me?
The question is
why it's you and me, of all people.
What's your date of birth?
Gyehae day, Gyeongja month, Byeongo year.
That's different from mine.
So are we turning to superstition?
Then, follow me.
You're a physician.
Can't you approach it scientifically?
Quiet. You'll bring bad energy.
There is
a virgin ghost in your body.
Do you see it?
Are you really seeing something?
That's why he knows
what women want better than women.
You.
You're a philanderer, aren't you?
Get up. Let's go.
Let's do a ritual.
I will exorcise the ghost.
Listen,
I have no intention
of letting this lady leave my body.
Why don't we try the ritual?
Once the spirit is out of the body,
we can see what we can do.
What if it never comes back?
I have no interest
in seeing the other world.
What if it wasn't our souls
that were switched,
but our bodies?
What?
In that case, we must use our bodies.
Take my hand, sincerely and solemnly.
Do you feel anything?
Not at all.
You said we should use our bodies.
Just holding hands won't do anything.
So what do you suggest we do?
Don't take this the wrong way.
Take what?
Could you try to meet me halfway?
What?
Right.
Do you feel anything?
Yes, it's quite loud.
I didn't know my heartbeat was so loud.
Is this a joke to you?
I like the sound of it.
Listen to it all you want
when you're back.
So it's not our bodies either.
What time was it when we were switched?
Around the curfew hour yesterday.
Is that when we will switch back?
Is this just a nightmare?
It's the curfew hour!
It seems like the nightmare...
...will be a long one.
Blast.
Earlier, you said it couldn't be
the work of a human.
That means nothing a human does will help.
Can we even continue to live like this?
Without knowing
when we'll be switched back?
Your Highness, there you were!
Your Highness's quarters
are in great uproar.
It's you again.
I will say no more.
Your face said it all.
What?
It's obvious
that I'm the one being dragged out.
And you look like
you're about to blame me.
Blame this wretch. He clung to me.
This wretch?
Remember whose mouth
you're using to speak now.
If it's right, does it matter
whose mouth says it?
Look.
Ignore him and talk to me, sir.
- Pardon?
- I mean, talk to me.
Yes.
The palace is in an uproar right now.
Why?
Her Majesty has ordered you
to return at once.
Her Majesty? Why?
Tell Her Majesty that
he can't go right now
due to the circumstances.
It is not your place to meddle.
He only listens to you. You say it.
You?
Her Majesty stopped eating last night
and says she will not eat
until you're there.
Because of me?
Who else could it be?
What trouble did you get yourself into?
There's no dignity,
grace or any pretext whatsoever.
Why does it have to be revealed
when I'm in this body?
Go and tell Her Majesty
that he's coming back.
So...
It seems like you must go back,
Your Highness.
Your Highness?
Yes, that's you.
The Grand Prince.
So, you're saying
you're the late King's second son?
Yes.
And the young brother
of His Majesty, the current king.
That's right.
In other words,
you're the prince of Joseon.
You seem pretty surprised.
'Cause I'm handsome, like the rumors say?
You woke up in a palace.
I thought you'd guess that much.
You've become really quiet.
I don't know what to say either.
I can't help but hold my tongue
under the weight
of the Grand Prince's name.
Don't be like that. It's not like you.
I'm trying to remember
everything I've said so far.
Would any of that
be considered high treason?
If that is the case,
would I be granted time to atone?
Just act as usual.
Act as usual and get my head chopped off?
Is that a joke?
All my life,
I've never been anywhere
near the royal family, ever.
Then, all of a sudden,
I'm here with someone
at the very center of the royal family,
at its very top.
Imagine how shocked I must be.
That is exactly why I didn't tell you.
Because I knew it would make anyone
feel pressured and uncomfortable.
I didn't hide it
because it was impressive or anything.
This is my royal command.
Treat me like before.
And I tolerate no disobedience.
When I woke up in the palace,
I thought you were here on work
because you're an aide.
Who'd think the palace is your home?
There are probably no more
than a dozen people who live there.
There are more than ten, at least.
I'm not in a position to say this,
because I lied too,
but this is just not a good time.
You can refuse if you want.
What?
How could you say something so unfilial
when your mother is refusing to eat?
The owner of that body
isn't exactly a filial son anyway.
So do you want me
to starve the Queen of this country
to death?
I'm not refusing to go.
I'm asking what I should do.
Come on. It's almost dawn.
Just do as I say.
First, put your hands behind your back.
Keep your back straight at all times,
and look as arrogant as possible.
What?
Didn't you say he was coming?
There comes His Highness.
She must be Her Majesty.
Don't be nervous. Just do as I was told.
Whatever I say, it doesn't come from me.
It seems Your Majesty's stubbornness
deepens with age.
Why did you stop eating?
It'll only ruin your fair face.
Where did you sleep the last two nights?
I can't believe this.
My harsh words didn't surprise her at all.
Somewhere where the sky is my roof
and the wind is my blanket.
With that lady as your companion?
That lady?
Hey, you didn't mention any lady.
Who is she?
I don't know either.
Then, who knows?
Last night, I saw you
frolicking around the palace,
hand in hand with this lady.
Your Majesty, it's a misunderstanding.
There is nothing between that lady and me.
I only met her once.
No, I didn't meet her only once.
I met her twice.
Don't look so flustered.
Dignity.
I will ask her myself.
Which family does she belong to?
Play innocent.
I don't know. I really don't.
Must I question all ladies in this country
to get you to talk?
Tell her it was just one night's fun
so you don't know her name.
It was just one night's fun
so I don't know her name.
What?
Are you saying you indulged in
so-called free love,
like the rabble?
- I'm one of them.
What?
How dare you?
I apologize for making your son like that.
No, I mean...
I apologize for acting like the rabble.
You're the Grand Prince.
You are to be virtuous
and serve as an example.
Send for the royal physician at once.
You're unwell as it is.
Why did you stop eating
and make things worse...
That's what His Highness said
over and over
because he was so deeply concerned.
So it just rolled off my tongue.
Right. I did do that.
Are you all right?
Get your hands off me.
What a scoundrel.
How dare you treat a precious young lady
as a mere one-night stand?
That is not how I raised you.
If you have any respect for me,
at least pretend to obey the confinement.
I will do so.
You're a court lady I haven't seen before.
Me?
I'm the new court lady
appointed to His Highness' quarters.
What is your name?
My name is Hong-si, Your Majesty.
Hong-si?
What's wrong with that?
CONDOLENCES
My condolences
on your grandfather's passing.
It's because the wrong woman
married into this family.
If you want a drink, come out.
Jae-i,
I'll pass on the drink.
Look over there.
She's Eun-jo's mother.
Could you let her see Eun-jo briefly?
I kept it secret
'cause she said she'd visit her mother.
It's my fault.
I caused Her Majesty's displeasure.
Don't worry. This isn't the first time.
We can't continue to stay together.
I must take your body
to your mother's place
by tomorrow morning.
Staying in the annex during mourning
isn't suspicious,
but tomorrow is the funeral.
You should at least show your face.
Could you do that for me?
You said you must keep it.
I don't understand what you must
keep through that marriage, though.
What about you?
Do you think you can be by yourself?
I should be able to.
We must find a way to go back
without disrupting our everyday lives.
Then, we need to pull another all-nighter.
Who is she?
Why does she act like a court lady?
What are they doing in there
for six hours?
Tell me about it.
As His Highness has ordered,
if this gets out,
everyone will be punished severely.
I think I've learned enough
about the people around you.
I'll handle the rest with my quick wits.
By the way...
Anything else you'd like to add?
I wasn't sure how to bring this up, but...
What is it?
Our bodies.
Let's say we didn't see anything.
I see.
Now you want privacy?
But we already saw everything.
No, I didn't see anything.
I'm not the one who saw it.
I saw it through your eyes,
so you're the one who saw it.
It sounds like you saw it very closely.
It's the same with my body.
You didn't touch my body.
It's my hands that touched my body.
Well...
Those are my memories, though.
Look here.
I'm confident.
You know what I mean.
I didn't see it.
I didn't see it through my eyes.
Now, call Dae-chu in.
What?
Are you avoiding my question?
I will walk from here.
People might see me.
Do as you please.
Dae-chu...
I mean,
Officer Seo.
Make sure you stay
by His Highness' side at all times.
See if he trembles with fear,
runs about flustered,
keeps to his meals,
or cries alone
at night.
Keep a close eye on him.
I don't need the advice. That's what I do.
Great then.
I know I should not meddle in matters
between a man and a woman...
I mean, I know it's beyond my concern,
but if you ever
hurt or take advantage of His Highness,
then I will step up.
Have you been always this cool
behind my back?
What?
You're one charming man.
Wait!
Stop what you were thinking.
YOUNG MASTER
MOTHER
Mother, Young Master.
What brings you here?
You little rascal.
Where have you been running around?
Young Master speaks before he thinks.
So ignore his harsh words.
He's kind by nature.
You could get kicked out for this.
That's exactly my wish.
What?
What matters is that she came back safely.
I went to tend to a sick patient.
That was very thoughtful of you.
You and your nosy nature.
Did you have to do this now?
The one who has passed is gone,
but the living must go on.
You don't even sound sad.
It's almost like you were waiting
for the Old Master to pass.
Look at her, Madam.
She didn't even answer.
I get it.
This is why you lied
about who you were marrying.
You must've been counting the days.
I should have known when you insisted,
despite Madam's objections.
Did I
hide it
even from my family?
Are you playing innocent now?
Be honest with me.
You just wanted a higher status.
Yes, apparently.
Madam.
Let's go.
We don't have to worry about her.
Can we talk for a moment?
All she cares about is me and my family.
So I married into this family
against your wishes.
Once you decide to do something,
you do it no matter what.
I didn't try to stop you again
because I knew you wouldn't listen.
I know that too well.
You raised one stubborn girl.
But now that I look back,
I may have used that
as an excuse to let you go.
I truly have no shame.
I really don't understand.
How is your daughter
supposed to feel right now?
You poor thing.
Of course, you don't understand.
It's because you buried everything
beneath the words "I'm fine."
You buried your heart.
Your Highness.
I watched her go in.
You must be tired. Get some rest.
By the way,
I learned something
while searching for Your Highness.
Do you know
who that woman
was wed to?
I ended up finding out
without meaning to.
I wish I'd never found out.
Your Highness,
are you all right?
I'm fine.
I will be fine.
Does this mean
she always puts others before herself?
It's all my fault.
All I ever taught her
was to endure and hold on.
I'm sorry, Eun-jo.
It seems like my mother is the one
I must protect.
No, don't.
Take this.
I borrowed it from the Director
of the Office of Royal Decrees.
What's this money for?
As you said,
you're a concubine in a powerful family,
so you'll live comfortably
without worrying about food or money.
But listen, Eun-jo.
If you ever
come to regret
your comfortable life
and want to run away,
take this.
I hear that no one can find
those who flee to the Ming.
Don't think about me or the lord
and go wherever you wish.
Could you give your mother
that one promise?
The beautiful daughter you know
would have made the promise.
But right now,
I can promise you this.
What is it?
I'll make sure
she never has to lift a finger.
How is that thing going?
I used the name
of a thief called Gil-dong.
Gil-dong?
He's the one who robbed
the Chief Censor's storehouse.
The Chief Censor spoke bitterly about him,
even to his last days,
so no one will find it suspicious.
Black Sword.
How are things at the constabulary?
They're investigating
those around the Chief Censor.
Keep a close watch over it.
Do not delegate this.
Yes, sir.
Is it this country
that you covet?
How dare you?
Do you have no fear of consequences?
If His Majesty finds out,
your entire family,
all three generations, will be quartered.
If you wish to live,
give me half of Joseon.
Greed
leads only to destruction
in the hands of the foolish.
Engrave these words upon your heart,
though that heart will soon rot away.
I can run into other royal family members
during the day,
so I will learn my way around the palace
while everyone's asleep.
Lady Jang.
She must be Geum-nok.
I've heard many rumors about her.
I smell medicinal herbs.
Where is it coming from?
I've never smelled anything like this.
The smoke from burning medicinal herbs
can ease certain symptoms,
but filling a room with so much smoke
that it spills outside
can be dangerous.
Who is getting this treatment?
"Gangnyeong Hall."
His Majesty's bedchamber.
Avoid His Majesty at all costs.
No.
Wrong time to be nosy,
wrong person to be nosy with.
GANGNYEONG HALL
Your Highness.
Quiet.
No one must know that I'm here.
Yes, Your Highness.
About the treatment
His Majesty is receiving...
The sound.
I beg your pardon, Your Majesty.
He suffers from skin affliction?
Yes, Your Highness.
What's the matter?
I said be quiet.
You'll awaken His Majesty.
Your Majesty?
You wanted to check the medicinal herbs?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I was going for a walk and...
Your Majesty,
we need to get the smoke out first.
Help me air the room.
You too, now.
What are you doing?
Your Majesty,
when overused,
any treatment can cause side effects.
Are you questioning
the royal physician's treatment?
I wouldn't dare.
But in my experience,
for skin afflictions,
a tonic brewed with cattle gallstones
and honeysuckle,
along with ointment and fresh air,
are most effective.
I meant you shouldn't rely
only on new herbs,
but use these proven treatments as well.
You seem to know
quite a bit about my condition.
You seem disappointed.
Because it isn't fatal enough to kill me.
Pardon?
That's not what it is.
In the thick smoke,
I could see Your Majesty's suffering.
What?
This skin affliction may appear
as small scars on the surface,
but it slowly erodes
the patient's everyday life.
And when prolonged,
it erodes their life as a whole.
The scar on the patient's body
scars their hearts as well.
So in hopes of easing that burden,
even a little,
I forgot my place and spoke out of turn.
You sounded pretty sincere.
I was almost moved.
Go now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
That was His Majesty?
Is he not on good terms
with the Grand Prince?
I should go back to my chamber now.
It's already the curfew...
Things have been so hectic
that I completely forgot about Gil-dong.
I wonder if they caught
the actual murderer.
I can't leave the palace
because I'm under confinement.
What do I do?
What do you mean, it's not Gil-dong?
His name was written in blood.
We're investigating those
who may have grudges against the offender.
Did you just call my husband
"offender"?
He died an unjust death!
How dare you call him an offender?
How dare you?
Escort her home.
Yes, sir.
Let go of me!
Gil-dong?
Get him!
Gil-dong, this wretch!
Don't kill him. We must take him alive!
Sir.
Inform His Highness of this at once.
Yes, sir.
Chief Secretary Im Sa-hyeong's family.
Somehow, I'm peeking into
the most private family affairs
of Joseon's greatest schemer.
Lady Jang?
What are you doing here,
dressed like that?
It seems Grand Prince Dowol
found out about the herbs.
Grand Prince Dowol?
Yes.
All the incense was removed.
What was that?
Why would my name
even come up in their conversation?
- Oh, no. He's caught?
- They caught Gil-dong.
- Gil-dong?
- Gil-dong was taken to the constabulary.
This is so frustrating.
Eun-jo!
Eun-jo.
Are you coming from the burial rites?
How are you feeling? Are you all right?
Yes.
By the way, Gil-dong was caught?
I just heard about it too.
Gil-dong was shot with an arrow yesterday.
What?
Eun-jo.
His Highness has disappeared again?
I didn't hear any cough so I checked,
and he was already gone.
The case is closed.
Yes, sir.
Wait!
Physician Hong.
This was Gil-dong?
His Highness folded the bedding
and the clothes this neatly?
That's not the only thing.
He was cleaning!
This is a grave matter.
Find His Highness!
Did something happen?
You scared me.
Where have you been?
I went to the Royal Pharmacy.
To have the tonic prepared
for Her Majesty.
Pardon?
I think I should do that much
to ease my guilt.
Why did you fold the bedding
and the nightclothes?
Because I woke up.
You could have summoned us.
Did Your Highness
put on your clothes yourself as well?
Yes, so you could sleep longer.
Please tell us if we have done
anything wrong, Your Highness!
You did nothing wrong.
Bring in the royal physician at once.
Why are you doing this?
Your Highness,
Officer Park has reached the constabulary.
Have they already received the message?
He was struck by an arrow
and died on the spot.
Gil-dong has died?
And the fake Gil-dong?
It's taken care of.
Take care of the rest with your own hands.
Yes, sir.
It's finished.
Farewell, Gil-dong.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Someone might come to collect
the fake Gil-dong's body.
They were stored carefully.
Those...
I did that?
I kept them carefully?
Give me a break.
What am I to do with this?
Should I have read the room
and waited before entering?
Yes. From now on,
count to ten before you enter.
When you look at me,
I see turmoil in your eyes.
What are you trying to do?
I'm trying to say nothing should be done.
The Grand Prince keeps getting in the way.
You there, Grand Prince's court lady.
Halt.
Subtitle translation by Sunyoung Baek